Date Ordered: 2016/04/28 11:48:33 +0000
Job: j166421
Name: OpenStreetMap: Manchester, England Metro Region
Data Listing Token: 2b454e92-67dd-4ff4-861a-051bea3de6fe
Job Token: 5eff76c2-ca30-4374-a681-be28bb71ba77


### Contents of Data Order ###

# Data #
The Data folder contains the data that was ordered. The file extension depends on the type of data requested.

# Misc #
The Misc folder contains any additional information the provider included with the dataset. If the provider did not include any additional information, this folder will be empty.

# Description #
The Description File is a copy of the dataset's description as seen on the data listing when the data was ordered.

# Read Me #
The file you are currently reading.

# License #
The License agreement associated with the downloaded data. The license agreement contains information on use restrictions, liability, and disclaimers.